Raymond Spilman Papers
Raymond Spilman Papers
- Tapes
  - Renwick, William / William Renwick IDSA early years of USID 7 of 7, 2/91; 107 (Box 92)
  - Schmeck, Robert / 3 Schmeck 4 / A: Obrig Mueller Doug Margilais[?] G. Lippincott Larry Bruelin Procedures/PB; B: Procedures/PB Bel Geddes, 038 (Box 92)
  - Schmeck, Robert / 5-6 Robert Schmeck formative years of USID, 7/28/78; 039 (Box 92)
  - Schmeck, Robert / Robert Schmeck on the formative years of USID, 7/28/78; 037 (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / [no title on spine] (80), 080 (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / initial concept and theme dedication of [IDH] bio program to Joe Seniel [sic], 010 (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / [no title on spine] Jo final interview art design Morris chair, Cc (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / [no title on spine] Jo Sinel Done IDHS 0-649, Kk (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / [no title on spine] Jo Sniel [sic] interviewed by unknown student date? WC, Ee (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / [no title on spine] RS - Sinel '93 1 & 2, Dd (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / [no title on spine] Sinel '93 3 & 4, Ff (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / [no title on spine] Sinel 5 & 6, Gg (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / [no title on spine] Sinel - 7 Sinel - 8, Hh (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / [no title on spine] Sinel - done Morris - To be done - 5 & 6, Ii (Box 92)
  - Sinel, Jo / [no title on spine] Student interview no date B Morris, Jj (Box 92)
  - Smith, Robert Glenn / Robert Glenn Smith FIDSA Anedotes [sic], 8/27/93; 095B; 4 copies (Box 92)
  - Smith, Robert Glenn / Robert Glenn Smith FIDSA formative years superceded by 93, 9/1/93; 095A; 3 copies (Box 92)
  - Spilman, Raymond / RS Bio about N.Y. - own office - H. Dreyfuss, 2/27/78; 063; 2 copies (Box 92)
  - Spilman, Raymond / RS History 1938-50 R.S. & H.D. [Sharon] Ryder Req., 128 (Box 92)
  - Steinhilber, Budd / Budd Steinhilber formative years of USID, 11/1/90; 091 (Box 92)
  - Teague, Dorwin / Dorwin Teague I.D. History Inter., 8/23/78; 040; 3 copies (Box 92)
  - Teague, Dorwin / Tape 2 Interview of Dorwin Teague by N. Polites at Nyack, 10/22/66; 096 (Box 92)
  - Vassos, John / An Afternoon with John Vassos Comstock Hill, 7/13/78; 046 (Box 92)
  - Vassos, John / J. Vassos on Dreyfuss; Monty Farrar Detroit, Dec 1972; 016 (Box 92)
  - Vassos, John / John Vassos Bio & H. D. - mem[?] M. Ferar - I.D.S.A., 12/22/72; 041 (Box 92)
  - Vassos, John / John Vassos RCA Brain Conversation with J.V. Tel -2-12-76, 042 (Box 92)
  - Vassos, John / Special tape for USID Philly 76 also part of I.D. history USID - RS only - Smithsonian [side title mentions HD-RS interview], G (Box 92)
  - Vassos, John / Vassos at Silvermine Norwalk also V. retro, 2/25/77; 045 (Box 92)
  - Vassos, John / Vassos I.D. Retro. Hose Retro to 231 J.V. on H.Dreyfuss 37 bio on J.V., 043; 2 copies (Box 92)
  - Viemeister, Read / Reid Viemeister [sic] FIDSA early years, 1/28/90; 094 (Box 92)
  - Viemeister, Read / Reid Viemiester [sic] Early Years of USID 1927-53 taped from 90m, 1/28/90; M (Box 92)
  - Walsh, Frank / Mel Best, 1968; 1978; 003 / 004 (Box 92)
  - Why Should Art Be Free? I.D.H. Archives discussion [side title mentions Arthur BecVar], J (Box 92)
  - Wicker / Wicker RS intro. to USID slide show, E (Box 92)
  - Wright, Russel / [no title on spine] Russel Wright Dialogue IV, 7/12/75; S (Box 92)
  - Wright, Russel / Misc. conversation Russel Wright John Vassos / R. Loewy to G, photo R.S. interviews, 11/17/76; 12/15/76; 031 (Box 92)
  - Wurster, Dave / Dave Wurster IDH, 6/9/79; 049; 2 copies (Box 92)
  - Unidentified tapes, 4 tapes (Box 92)